worldofquotes.com 2013-06-30

# 

**Privacy Statement for WorldofQuotes.com**  
WorldofQuotes.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: WorldofQuotes.com 

**Information Automatically Logged**  
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes, mainly traffic analyses. 

**Cookies**  
Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. 

**Advertisers**  
Some broad customer data is shared with the advertising companies (number of visitors, countries of origin, average customer profile. 

**Personal Information**  
Email addresses collected on this site are only used for the daily random quote and for no other purpose. Your email address will never be sold/traded to anyone else. 

**External Links**  
This site contains links to other sites. WorldofQuotes.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

**Security**   
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us here
